<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/index.html</link>
    <description>WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI Documentation The WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit (WKT) is a collection of open source tools that help you provision WebLogic-based applications to run in Linux containers on a Kubernetes cluster. WKT includes the following tools:&#xA;WebLogic Deploy Tooling (WDT) - A set of single-purpose, lifecycle tools that operate off of a single metadata model representation of a WebLogic domain. WebLogic Image Tool (WIT) - A tool for creating Linux container images for running WebLogic domains. WebLogic Kubernetes Operator (WKO) - A Kubernetes operator that allows WebLogic domains to run natively in a Kubernetes cluster. The WKT User Interface (WKT UI) provides a graphical user interface that wraps the WKT tools, Docker, Helm, and the Kubernetes client (kubectl) and helps guide you through the process of creating and modifying a model of your WebLogic domain, creating a Linux container image to use to run the domain, and setting up and deploying the software and configuration necessary to deploy and access the domain in your Kubernetes cluster.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 14:09:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About the WKT UI Application</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/concepts/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/concepts/index.html</guid>
      <description>Contents WKT Project File Settings Outside the WKT Project File Environment Variables User Preferences Proxy Configuration GitHub API Credentials Linux Disable Hardware Acceleration AppImage WKT Tools Configuration Logging Configuration Startup Internet Connectivity Test Configuration WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI Introduction Configuration External Applications Bundled WKT Applications Before giving you the whirlwind tour of the WKT UI application, it is important to know that the application is a native, desktop application. It uses native operating system features, such as:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Started</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/index.html</guid>
      <description>PrerequisitesInstall the prerequisite requirements.&#xA;Install WKT UIInstall the WKT UI application and check for updates.&#xA;Quick Start GuideUse the Quick Start guide to exercise WKT UI functionality and deploy a sample application.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigate the UI</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/index.html</guid>
      <description>Before you begin Make sure you have read About the WKT UI Application .&#xA;About the UI To help you understand how to use the WKT UI, we will step you through it, section by section, describing the important decisions to make and fields to populate. The sections are listed in the left side navigation pane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Guide</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/developer/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/developer/index.html</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI is a desktop application designed to help WebLogic users move their applications to run in a Kubernetes environment.&#xA;Setting up your development environment Download and install the latest LTS version of node.js from https://nodejs.org/en/download/ .&#xA;If you rely on a proxy server to reach the Internet, set these five environment variables to configure the proxy correctly:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 14:09:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 2.0.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features Replaced the WebLogic Remote Console integration with a new, integrated WDT model editor. #308, #323 - Added support for cross-architecture container images. #326 - Centralized container image registry credentials to eliminate the need to re-enter the same credentials multiple times. Other Changes Removed support for Verrazzano. Removed auto-update restrictions on Linux RPM and DEB installers, leveraging a beta feature in Electron Updater. #292 - Removed support for the deprecated keytar module that allowed storing credentials in the OS credential store. #307 - Removed support for Domain-in-Image and Model-in-Image without an Auxiliary Image. #323 - Added support for AppImage to store WDT and WIT tool updates in an external directory. #331 - Added user preferences option to disable Linux hardware acceleration in Chromium. #337 - Added support for overriding the default WKO Kubernetes CPU and memory requests and limits. #339 - Added user preferences option to provide a GitHub API token to bypass anonymous GitHub API rate limits. #458 - Added project settings options for model archive zip file handling to allow using archive files larger than 2 GB. #480 - Added an OPatch Bug Number field to support the WebLogic Image Tool’s --opatchBugNumber argument when creating a primary image, if needed. The new, embedded WebLogic Image Tool 1.16.3 makes it unlikely the user will need to use it. #481 - Removed the default value for the DOCKER_BUILDKIT environment variable and allowing it to be passed from the user’s environment, if needed. Bug Fixes #334 - Updated Ingress route support to work with current versions of the supported ingress controllers. #429 - Added support for ServerTemplate-defined keystores to the Archive Editor. #442 - Removed RPM installer dependency on java-atk-wrapper to support Oracle Linux 9.0+. Known Issues None</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>