<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Client Configuration</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/kubernetes/k8s-client-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/kubernetes/k8s-client-config/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Client Configuration  Authentication with Managed Kubernetes Clusters Verify Connectivity    Client Configuration Client Configuration helps you get the necessary connectivity to your Kubernetes cluster. Use the Kubernetes Cluster Type field to select the target Kubernetes cluster type to show instructions for configuring kubectl to successfully connect to the cluster.
 The Kubectl Executable to Use field tells the WKT UI application where to find the correct version of kubectl to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client Configuration</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-client-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-client-config/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Client Configuration  Authentication with Managed Kubernetes Clusters Verify Connectivity    Client Configuration Client Configuration helps you get the necessary connectivity to your Kubernetes cluster. Use the Kubernetes Cluster Type field to select the target Kubernetes cluster type to show instructions for configuring kubectl to successfully connect to the cluster.
 The Kubectl Executable to Use field tells the WKT UI application where to find the correct version of kubectl to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Kubernetes Cluster Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-kubernetes/k8s-client-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-kubernetes/k8s-client-config/</guid>
      <description>First, you need to configure your Kubernetes client (kubectl) to connect and authenticate to your Kubernetes cluster.
Go to the Kubernetes &amp;gt; Client Configuration page, shown in the following image.
By selecting the appropriate Kubernetes Cluster Type, the instructions panel will display the steps needed to properly configure kubectl. Select your Kubernetes Cluster Type and follow the instructions (including the linked instructions) until you can successfully connect using kubectl from the command line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Kubernetes Cluster Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-verrazzano/vz-client-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-verrazzano/vz-client-config/</guid>
      <description>First, you need to configure your Kubernetes Client (kubectl) to connect and authenticate to your Kubernetes cluster.
Go to the Verrazzano &amp;gt; Client Configuration page, as shown in the following image.
By selecting the appropriate Kubernetes Cluster Type, the instructions panel will display the steps needed to properly configure kubectl. Please select your Kubernetes Cluster Type and follow the instructions (including the linked instructions) until you can successfully connect using kubectl from the command line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offline Discover</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-advanced/offline-discover/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-advanced/offline-discover/</guid>
      <description>In WKTUI, go to the Model page and select the Code View tab. Select the File &amp;gt; Add Model &amp;gt; Discover Model (offline) menu item. The following dialog box appears. Enter the path to the $WKTUI_QS_HOME/todolist_domain directory as the Domain Home, as shown in the following image.
To start the discovery process, click OK. After it completes, make the following required model changes:
 Fill in the credentials using the values provided when you ran the startMySQL and createToDoListDomain scripts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/prerequisites/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/prerequisites/</guid>
      <description>WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI has a number of prerequisites that must be installed locally to fully use the WKT UI application functionality.
These include:
 Java Development Kit (JDK) - Required by both WebLogic Deploy Tooling and WebLogic Image Tool. Install a JDK version that is compatible with your local WebLogic Server installation. WebLogic Server (WLS) - Required by WebLogic Deploy Tooling. Install a WebLogic Server version 12.2.1.3.0 or later; it is a best practice to install the latest Patch Set Updates (PSUs) and other recommended patches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/prereqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/prereqs/</guid>
      <description>To work through the Quick Start guide, you will need to install the following software:
 Docker (or Podman) – If running on Windows or macOS, try Rancher Desktop, Docker Desktop, or even Podman Desktop. kubectl – The Kubernetes client; the version should align with the Kubernetes cluster version. Oracle Java JDK 11 WebLogic Server 14.1.1 Helm 3.9 or later – Only needed if following the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator track. Maven 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Settings</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/project-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/project-settings/</guid>
      <description>The first stop for every new project is Project Settings. In this section, you make decisions and provide input for the project on:
 Credential Storage Domain Location Kubernetes Environment Target Type JDK and WebLogic Server Installation Directories Image Build Tool Type and Executable Location  When running the WKT UI application on Windows or Linux, the application inherits its environment from the user. For example, adding a directory to the PATH used by the application is just a matter of changing your PATH environment variable and restarting the application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get the ToDo List sample application</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/get-todo-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/get-todo-app/</guid>
      <description>The Quick Start tutorial employs a simple ToDo List application that uses a MySQL database running in a container to maintain its state. To get the application and supporting files, use one of the following methods:
  Download the quickstart.zip or quickstart.tar.gz file from the latest WKTUI release on GitHub.
  Clone the WKTUI GitHub repository and refer to the samples/quickstart subdirectory.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-kubernetes/k8s-wko/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-kubernetes/k8s-wko/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Kubernetes Operator (WKO) manages WebLogic or FMW domains for a set of namespaces in a Kubernetes cluster. While it is possible to install multiple operators that manage disparate sets of namespaces in a Kubernetes cluster, typically, there is no need to do this.
To install the operator, go to the Kubernetes &amp;gt; WebLogic Operator page, verify the settings, and click Install Operator. For these exercises, you&amp;rsquo;ll use the default values, as shown in the following image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Verrazzano</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-verrazzano/vz-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-verrazzano/vz-install/</guid>
      <description>To install Verrazzano, go to the Verrazzano &amp;gt; Installation page. Set the Release Version field to the newest version listed, set the other fields to match those in the following image, and click Install Verrazzano.
Verrazzano installation takes some time to complete, typically 15 to 30 minutes. Use Check Verrazzano Install Status to determine when Verrazzano installation is complete. After it&amp;rsquo;s complete, you can move on to the next section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-install/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Verrazzano Design View Code View Install Verrazzano Check Verrazzano Installation Status  Verrazzano This section provides support for installing Verrazzano in the target Kubernetes cluster. For detailed information about Verrazzano, see the Verrazzano documentation.
Design View Design View helps you specify the data needed to install Verrazzano to manage WebLogic domains in one or more Kubernetes namespaces. To install Verrazzano, simply provide values for the following fields:
 Install Name - The name to give the Verrazzano object during installation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Model</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/model/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/model/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Model Design View Code View  Model Editor Variables Editor Archive Editor   Validate Model Prepare Model  Model The Model section helps you work with WebLogic Deploy Tooling models for a WebLogic domain. A WebLogic Deploy Tooling model for a domain can include the following file types:
 Model file - A declarative definition of the domain configuration. Variable file - A property file that maps names to values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Remote Discover</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-advanced/online-remote-discover/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-advanced/online-remote-discover/</guid>
      <description>In WKTUI, go to the Model page and select the Code View tab. Select the File &amp;gt; Add Model &amp;gt; Discover Model (online) menu item. The following dialog box appears. Enter the information shown in the following image, including the Domain Home path $WKTUI_QS_HOME/todolist_domain directory. Make sure to provide the WebLogic user name and password specified when you ran the createToDoListDomain script.
This path is used to present the results of what we need to do, as shown in the following image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/kubernetes/k8s-wko/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/kubernetes/k8s-wko/</guid>
      <description>Contents  WebLogic Kubernetes Operator Design View  WebLogic Kubernetes Operator Image Image Pull Secret Kubernetes Namespace Selection Strategy WebLogic Kubernetes Operator Role Bindings External REST API Access Third Party Integrations Java Logging   Code View Install Operator Update Operator Uninstall Operator  WebLogic Kubernetes Operator This section provides support for installing the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator (the &amp;ldquo;operator&amp;rdquo;) in the target Kubernetes cluster. For detailed information about the operator, see the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Component</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-component/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-component/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Verrazzano Component Design View  Primary Image to Use for the Domain Auxiliary Image to Use for the Domain Clusters Model Variables Overrides Secrets Runtime Encryption Secret WebLogic Kubernetes Operator Introspection Configuration Domain-Wide Server Settings Domain-Wide Node Selector   Code View Prepare Model Deploy Component Undeploy Component  Verrazzano Component The Component section provides support for creating and deploying the Verrazzano component for the WebLogic domain.
Design View Design View helps you specify the data needed to generate the component definition and deploy that resource into a Kubernetes cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy the Domain</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-kubernetes/k8s-weblogic-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-kubernetes/k8s-weblogic-domain/</guid>
      <description>To inform the operator of a new WebLogic or FMW domain, you must create an operator Domain resource object in Kubernetes. Starting in WKO 4.0.0, the operator also needs an operator Cluster resource object for every cluster in the domain. This separation is required to work with the Kubernetes Horizontal Pod Autoscaler (HPA) to allow it to automatically scale clusters based on load (but only up to the maximum size of the WebLogic cluster).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy the Verrazzano Component for the WebLogic Domain</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-verrazzano/vz-component/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-verrazzano/vz-component/</guid>
      <description>Verrazzano installation includes the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator. To inform the operator about a new WebLogic or FMW domain, you need to create a Verrazzano component that includes an operator Domain resource object in Kubernetes. Starting in Verrazzano 1.5.0, the Verrazzano component also needs an operator Cluster resource object for every cluster in the domain. This separation is required to work with the Kubernetes Horizontal Pod Autoscaler (HPA) to allow it to automatically scale the clusters based on load (but only up to the maximum size of the WebLogic cluster).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/image/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/image/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Image Design View  Target Image Name and Registry Credentials Base Image to Use Installers for Building the Image Patch Oracle Home WebLogic Deploy Tooling Configuration Image Build Configuration   Code View Create Images Push Images  Image The Image section helps you build container images for deploying WebLogic-based applications in a Kubernetes environment using the WebLogic Image Tool.
Design View Design View helps you specify the necessary data needed to run the WebLogic Image Tool to build an image for running the WebLogic domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install WKT UI</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/install/</guid>
      <description>Download the latest WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI (WKT UI) application installers from the GitHub Releases section of this repository. Simply run the appropriate installer for your operating system.  Each release has many assets, some of which are needed for the application’s auto-update functionality and are not intended to be used for installing the application. The following table lists the installer file names and their purpose.
   Installer File Name Purpose     WebLogic-Kubernetes-Toolkit-UI-1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set up the WKTUI application</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/set-up-wktui-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/set-up-wktui-app/</guid>
      <description>To install the WKTUI application:
 Make sure to check the NOTE in the WKTUI Prerequisites for your OS compatibility with regard to Electron support. Go to the GitHub project Releases page and download the latest release. Run the appropriate installer for your operating system.  Each release has many assets. For a detailed description of them, see Install WKT UI.
WKTUI Startup WKTUI requires Internet connectivity, not only for proper UI rendering, but also for REST APIs calls that it makes to GitHub for detecting and downloading updates, when they are available, and for determining the available versions of related software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebLogic Domain</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/kubernetes/k8s-weblogic-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/kubernetes/k8s-weblogic-domain/</guid>
      <description>Contents  WebLogic Domain Design View  Primary Image to Use for the Domain Auxiliary Image to Use for the Domain Clusters Model Variables Overrides Secrets Runtime Encryption Secret WebLogic Kubernetes Operator Introspection Configuration Domain-Wide Server Settings Domain-Wide Node Selector   Code View Prepare Model Deploy Domain Get Domain Status Undeploy Domain  WebLogic Domain The WebLogic Domain section provides support for creating and deploying the Kubernetes custom resource for the WebLogic domain as defined by the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-application/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Verrazzano Application Design View  Components   Code View Deploy Application Undeploy Application  Verrazzano Application A Verrazzano application is comprised of Components. Components encapsulate application implementation details. For detailed information, see Applications in the Verrazzano documentation.
The Application section makes it easy to compose an application that includes the Component for the WebLogic domain.
Design View Design View provides values for defining the application and customizing it for the target environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy the Verrazzano Application</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-verrazzano/vz-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-verrazzano/vz-application/</guid>
      <description>A Verrazzano application is a list of components, each with zero or more traits attached. Go to the Verrazzano &amp;gt; Application page. Add all five components and fill out the remaining fields, as shown in the following figure.
Now, expand the todolist-domain component, enable Enable Ingress Trait, and click the plus sign on the Ingress Rules table. Fill in the resulting form with the data shown in the following image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ingress Controller</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/kubernetes/k8s-ingress-controller/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/kubernetes/k8s-ingress-controller/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Ingress Controller Design View  Ingress Controller Configuration TLS Secret for Ingress Routes Ingress Routes Configuration   Code View Install Ingress Controller Update Ingress Routes Uninstall Ingress Controller  Ingress Controller This section supports two distinct functions related to an ingress controller. First, it supports installing an ingress controller to a Kubernetes cluster. Second, it supports adding the necessary routes to an ingress controller to make a deployed WebLogic domain&amp;rsquo;s endpoints accessible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install and Configure the Ingress Controller</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-kubernetes/k8s-ingress-controller/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-kubernetes/k8s-ingress-controller/</guid>
      <description>While the domain is up and running, it is only accessible from inside the Kubernetes cluster. Before you can expose your application, you need to install an ingress controller. WKTUI can install the Traefik or NGINX ingress controllers. In this exercise, you will use Traefik.
Go to the Kubernetes &amp;gt; Ingress Controller page. Even though the default settings should be sufficient, you will create an image pull secret for Docker Hub, as shown in the following image, to make sure that your cluster doesn’t encounter an error due to Docker Hub rate limiting of anonymous pull requests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Select the Project Settings</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/project-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/project-settings/</guid>
      <description>Start WKTUI.
WKTUI uses the concept of a project that is like a project in an Integrated Development Environment (IDE). You will create a new project.
  Using the File menu, select New Project, choose a directory, and enter the file name todo-list.wktproj.
At this point, you will be on the Project Settings page that will look something like the one shown in the following image.
Note: If you are not running on macOS, you will not see this top-most panel: For macOS, do you need to add directories to the PATH or define other environment variables for Docker/Podman or Kubernetes?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access the ToDo List application</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-kubernetes/k8s-access-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-kubernetes/k8s-access-app/</guid>
      <description>After the Update Ingress Routes action completes, the Ingress Route Configuration table is updated with the actual URL to use to access the application, as shown in the following image.
When you click the URL link, the following image shows the browser window that WKTUI opens. Now, you can use the ToDo list application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access the ToDo List application</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-verrazzano/vz-access-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-verrazzano/vz-access-app/</guid>
      <description>After the application is deployed and the WebLogic Domain is up and running, click Update URLs to update the URL with the actual hostname, which will also activate the link, as shown in the following image.
Click on the link to go to your application, as shown in in the following image. Note that because your installation is using self-signed certificates, the browser will likely warn you that going to the application is unsafe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create the WebLogic Deploy Tooling model</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/create-wdt-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/create-wdt-model/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Deploy Tooling project provides a set of single-purpose tools for performing lifecycle operations of WebLogic Server domains. These tools work off a model of the domain. The model contains three types of files:
 Model file – A YAML description of the domain that is aligned with WebLogic Scripting Tool (WLST) offline folders and attributes. Variables file – An optional Java properties file that contains key/value pairs where the key matches with a token placed in the model file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create images with the WebLogic Image Tool</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/create-images-with-wit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/create-images-with-wit/</guid>
      <description>WKTUI uses the WebLogic Image Tool (WIT) to build container images. Each Oracle Fusion Middleware (FMW) Domain Target Location option has its own image requirements.
 Model-in-Image – MII has two approaches:  Single Image – This approach uses a single image with Java, FMW, WDT, and the WDT model files all built into a single image. In WKTUI, we use the Primary Image tab to build such an image. Dual Images – This approach puts Java and FMW into one image, which WKTUI calls the primary image, and WDT and the WDT model files into a separate image, known as the auxiliary image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.6.2</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.2/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.6.2  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #287 - Added support for WebLogic Kubernetes Operator domain specification&amp;rsquo;s precreateService setting.  Bug Fixes  #286 - Fixed an issue related to SSL termination and pass through Ingress resource generation.  Known Issues  On Linux, the open and save dialogs open behind the main application window. This is due to Electron bug 32857.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.6.3</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.3/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.6.3  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #294 - Updated Model Design View to use WebLogic Remote Console 2.4.8  Bug Fixes None
Known Issues  On Linux, the open and save dialogs open behind the main application window. This is due to Electron bug 32857. When deploying a Verrazzano application, the Get Application Status button only checks the status of the project&amp;rsquo;s Verrazzano component containing the WebLogic domain specification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.6.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.1/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.6.1  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #281 - Fixed issue with Ingress Controller shell script not using elif. #282 - Fixed issue with busy dialog referencing &amp;ldquo;auxiliary image&amp;rdquo; while building a domain creation image. #283 - Fixed a typo in the Verrazzano application page in its reference to the Manual Scaler trait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.5.3</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.3/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.5.3  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #242 - Added initial (very minimal) internationalization support bundles. #245 - Added an Ingress Controller Service Type field that can be used when installing an ingress controller to a Kubernetes cluster without a load balancer.  Bug Fixes  #241 - Fixed a bug with the WebLogic Image Tool&amp;rsquo;s --wdtHome argument when it ended with weblogic-deploy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes 1.6.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.6.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  This release has major usability changes to clearly delineate the following use cases:
 A project that contains a WDT model A project that does not have a model but uses an &amp;ldquo;external image&amp;rdquo; that contains a model A project with no model  When actions are not relevant to the use case, action buttons and Go menu items are hidden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.5.2</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.2/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.5.2  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #232 - Fixed an issue in the Verrazzano Application page where the component&amp;rsquo;s Ingress Trait Rule destination names were not properly converted to legal Kubernetes names so that they would match the generated service names when the domain, cluster, or server names combinations had more than one disallowed characters in them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.5.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.1/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.5.1  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #229 - Fixed issue in Domain resource generation on Windows inserting a path with Windows separators  Known Issues  In the Model Design View, changing the Source Path and Plan Path fields for existing App Deployments and Shared Libraries is broken in this release. To work around it, either remove and recreate the deployment or use the Model Code View&amp;rsquo;s Model Editor and Archive Editor to make the appropriate changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.5.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.5.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #202 - Added support for Verrazzano 1.5.0+ (which uses WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 4.0.0+). #204 - Updated the Archive Editor to align with WebLogic Deploy Tooling 3.0.0+ changes to the archive format. #205 - Added support for installing the optional Verrazzano component Argo CD with Verrazzano 1.5.0+. #205 - Added support to configure Kubernetes connectivity data for Verrazzano managed clusters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.4.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.4.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.4.1/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.4.1  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #192: Add the ability to install and work with older versions of operator using the latest published Helm chart.  Bug Fixes  Resolved issue Discover Model issue introduced in 1.4.0 by picking up the fix in WebLogic Deploy Tooling 2.4.1. Resolved issue with Deploy Domain failing due to a WebLogic Kubernetes Operator error from the new conversion/validating webhook (fix in a new published version of the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.4.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.4.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.4.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features  #173: Added support for WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 4.0. While it is now the default, versions 3.3+ are still supported.  Other Changes  #175: Added Zoom In, Zoom Out, and Actual Size menu options to the Window menu. #178: Integrated the Prepare Model action with the changes in WebLogic Deploy Tooling 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.3.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.3.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.3.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features  Support for creating and deploying the Verrazzano component for the WebLogic domain, and an application that references it.  Other Changes  Updated the WebLogic Remote Console integration to support version 2.4.0. Added support for specifying node selectors when installing the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator and deploying the WebLogic domain, either directly or as a Verrazzano component.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.2.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.2.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes  Major New Features  Model Design View added via integration with the WebLogic Remote Console 2.3.0. Users must download and install the WebLogic Remote Console version 2.3.x.  Other Changes  Added a new installer for macOS ARM. #141: Added support for WDT online remote discovery.  Bug Fixes  #107: Resolved an issue where the Save As functionality was not handling the archive file properly if there were no pending updates to the archive file (Jira WKTUI-322).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.1.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.1.1/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.1.1  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features No new features.
Other Changes  Revamped the Ingress Route editing mechanism:  Added busy dialog while fetching existing service data from the domain&amp;rsquo;s Kubernetes namespace prior to opening the route edit dialog. Added placeholders to the Target Service and Target Port fields to clarify the current state of these fields when no value is selected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.1.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.1.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features  Updated macOS environment control to specify extra environment settings to pass down to Docker/Podman, kubectl, and Helm invocations. Bundling WebLogic Deploy Tooling 2.0.0. See WDT release notes for details. New Validate Model action that leverages WDT 2.0 changes to validate the model files and reports any validation errors it finds. Updated Prepare Model action that leverages WDT 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
