<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Verrazzano on WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Verrazzano on WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Client Configuration</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-client-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-client-config/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Client Configuration  Authentication with Managed Kubernetes Clusters Verify Connectivity    Client Configuration Client Configuration helps you get the necessary connectivity to your Kubernetes cluster. Use the Kubernetes Cluster Type field to select the target Kubernetes cluster type to show instructions for configuring kubectl to successfully connect to the cluster.
 The Kubectl Executable to Use field tells the WKT UI application where to find the correct version of kubectl to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-install/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Verrazzano Design View Code View Install Verrazzano Check Verrazzano Installation Status  Verrazzano This section provides support for installing Verrazzano in the target Kubernetes cluster. For detailed information about Verrazzano, see the Verrazzano documentation.
Design View Design View helps you specify the data needed to install Verrazzano to manage WebLogic domains in one or more Kubernetes namespaces. To install Verrazzano, simply provide values for the following fields:
 Install Name - The name to give the Verrazzano object during installation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Component</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-component/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-component/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Verrazzano Component Design View  Primary Image to Use for the Domain Auxiliary Image to Use for the Domain Clusters Model Variables Overrides Secrets Runtime Encryption Secret WebLogic Kubernetes Operator Introspection Configuration Domain-Wide Server Settings Domain-Wide Node Selector   Code View Prepare Model Deploy Component Undeploy Component  Verrazzano Component The Component section provides support for creating and deploying the Verrazzano component for the WebLogic domain.
Design View Design View helps you specify the data needed to generate the component definition and deploy that resource into a Kubernetes cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/navigate/verrazzano/vz-application/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Verrazzano Application Design View  Components   Code View Deploy Application Undeploy Application  Verrazzano Application A Verrazzano application is comprised of Components. Components encapsulate application implementation details. For detailed information, see Applications in the Verrazzano documentation.
The Application section makes it easy to compose an application that includes the Component for the WebLogic domain.
Design View Design View provides values for defining the application and customizing it for the target environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
