<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quick Start Guide on WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quick Start Guide on WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/prereqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/prereqs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To work through the Quick Start guide, you will need to install the following software:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Docker (or Podman) – If running on Windows or macOS, try Rancher Desktop, Docker Desktop, or even Podman Desktop.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;kubectl&lt;/code&gt; – The Kubernetes client; the version should align with the Kubernetes cluster version.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Oracle Java JDK 8, 11, 17, or 21 to align with the version of WebLogic Server you plan to use.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;WebLogic Server 12.2.1.4, 14.1.1, 14.1.2, or 15.1.1&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Helm 3.9 or later&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Maven 3.6 or later – Only needed if rebuilding the sample application WAR file.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the ToDo List sample application</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/get-todo-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/get-todo-app/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Quick Start tutorial employs a simple ToDo List application that uses a MySQL database running in a container to maintain its state.&#xA;To get the application and supporting files, use one of the following methods:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Download the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/oracle/weblogic-toolkit-ui/releases/latest/downloads/quickstart.zip&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;quickstart.zip&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;or &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/oracle/weblogic-toolkit-ui/releases/latest/downloads/quickstart.tar.gz&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;quickstart.tar.gz&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; file&#xA;from the latest WKTUI 2.x.y release on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/oracle/weblogic-toolkit-ui/releases/latest/&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Clone the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/oracle/weblogic-toolkit-ui&#34;&gt;WKTUI GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt; and refer to the &lt;code&gt;samples/quickstart&lt;/code&gt; subdirectory.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up the WKTUI application</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/set-up-wktui-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/set-up-wktui-app/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To install the WKTUI application:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Make sure to check the NOTE in the WKTUI &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/prerequisites/&#34;&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/a&gt; for your OS compatibility with regard to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.npmjs.com/package/electron&#34;&gt;Electron&lt;/a&gt; support.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Go to the GitHub project &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/oracle/weblogic-toolkit-ui/releases&#34;&gt;Releases page&lt;/a&gt; and download the latest release.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Run the appropriate installer for your operating system.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each release has many assets. For a detailed description of them, see &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/install/&#34;&gt;Install WKT UI&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;important-note-for-macos-users&#34;&gt;Important Note for macOS Users&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Newer Mac machines use Apple Silicon CPUs, which are a type of ARM CPUs.  This guide uses the OCI Oracle Kubernetes Engine (OKE)&#xA;for deployment of the WebLogic Server domain.  By default, OKE nodes are provisioned using AMD (Intel-compatible) CPUs.&#xA;This will require using a new feature in WKTUI 2.0 that supports cross-architecture images.  Rancher Desktop (and most&#xA;other Docker providers) rely on QEMU (Quick Emulator) to support cross-architecture capabilities.  As of the writing of&#xA;this guide, Rancher Desktop with QEMU cross-architecture builds are not as reliable as we would like.  Our advice is to&#xA;open the Rancher Desktop &lt;code&gt;Preferences&lt;/code&gt; window, navigate to &lt;code&gt;Virtual Machine&lt;/code&gt; -&amp;gt; &lt;code&gt;Emulation&lt;/code&gt;, and change the&#xA;&lt;code&gt;Virtual Machine Type&lt;/code&gt; from &lt;code&gt;QEMU&lt;/code&gt; to &lt;code&gt;VZ&lt;/code&gt;.  The author also checked the &lt;code&gt;VZ Option&lt;/code&gt; to &lt;code&gt;Enable Rosetta support&lt;/code&gt;, though&#xA;this is probably not required.  This will provide a more reliable cross-architecture container image building environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Select the Project Settings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/project-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/project-settings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Start WKTUI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WKTUI uses the concept of a project that is like a project in an Integrated Development Environment (IDE).  You will create a new project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Using the &lt;code&gt;File&lt;/code&gt; menu, select &lt;code&gt;New Project&lt;/code&gt;, choose a directory, and enter the file name &lt;code&gt;todo-list.wktproj&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At this point, you will be on the &lt;code&gt;Project Settings&lt;/code&gt; page that will look something like the one shown in the following image.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: If you are &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt;  running on macOS, you will not see this top-most panel: For macOS, do you need to add directories to the PATH or define other environment variables for Docker/Podman or Kubernetes?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create the WebLogic Deploy Tooling model</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/create-wdt-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/create-wdt-model/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The WebLogic Deploy Tooling project provides a set of single-purpose tools for performing lifecycle operations of WebLogic Server domains.  These tools work off a model of the domain.  The model contains three types of files:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Model file – A YAML description of the domain that is aligned with WebLogic Scripting Tool (WLST) offline folders and attributes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Variables file – An optional Java properties file that contains key/value pairs where the key matches with a token placed in the model file.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Archive file – An optional ZIP file that contains any file artifacts that need to exist in the domain, for example, a WAR file that contains the binaries for a Web application.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more detailed WDT information, see the WebLogic Deploy Tooling &lt;a href=&#34;https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/concepts/model/&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create images with the WebLogic Image Tool</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/create-images-with-wit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/create-images-with-wit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WKTUI uses the WebLogic Image Tool (WIT) to build container images.  Each Oracle Fusion Middleware (FMW) Domain Target Location option has its own image requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Model-in-Image – MII has two approaches:&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Single Image – This approach uses a single image with Java, FMW, WDT, and the WDT model files all built into a single image.  In WKTUI, we use the &lt;code&gt;Primary Image&lt;/code&gt; tab to build such an image.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dual Images – This approach puts Java and FMW into one image, which WKTUI calls the primary image, and WDT and the WDT model files into a separate image, known as the auxiliary image.  In this document, we refer to this as MII with Auxiliary Image.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Domain-in-Image – DII uses a single image approach but uses WDT and the WDT model files to create the domain inside the image.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Domain-on-PV – DoPV uses a single image with Java and FMW in it.  The domain is created on the persistent volume by external means.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Both MII with Auxiliary Image and Domain-on-PV have an image containing only software (Java and FMW) with no configuration.  This provides several important, operational advantages:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
