<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quick Start Guide :: WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/index.html</link>
    <description>Use the Quick Start guide to exercise WKT UI functionality and deploy a sample application.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/prereqs/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/prereqs/index.html</guid>
      <description>To work through the Quick Start guide, you will need to install the following software:&#xA;Docker (or Podman) – If running on Windows or macOS, try Rancher Desktop, Docker Desktop, or even Podman Desktop. kubectl – The Kubernetes client; the version should align with the Kubernetes cluster version. Oracle JDK 8, 11, 17, or 21 to align with the version of WebLogic Server you plan to use. WebLogic Server 14.1.1, 14.1.2, or 15.1.1 Helm 3.9 or later Maven 3.6 or later – Only needed if rebuilding the sample application WAR file. Note that while the sample application can run on WebLogic Server 12.2.1.4, you will need to change the quickstart/app/src/main/webapp/WEB-INF/web.xml deployment descriptor to point to the Java EE 7 Web Application 3.1 specification and rebuild the binary by running mvn clean package in the quickstart/app directory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the ToDo List sample application</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/get-todo-app/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/get-todo-app/index.html</guid>
      <description>The Quick Start tutorial employs a simple ToDo List application that uses a MySQL database running in a container to maintain its state. To get the application and supporting files, use one of the following methods:&#xA;Download the quickstart.zip or quickstart.tar.gz file from the latest WKT UI 2.x.y release on GitHub .&#xA;Clone the WKT UI GitHub repository and refer to the samples/quickstart subdirectory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up the WKT UI application</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/set-up-wktui-app/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/set-up-wktui-app/index.html</guid>
      <description>To install the WKT UI application:&#xA;Make sure to check the NOTE in the WKT UI Prerequisites for your OS compatibility with regard to Electron support. Go to the GitHub project Releases page and download the latest release. Run the appropriate installer for your operating system. Each release has many assets. For a detailed description of them, see Install WKT UI .&#xA;Important Note for macOS Users Newer Mac machines use Apple Silicon CPUs, which are a type of ARM CPUs. This guide uses the OCI Oracle Kubernetes Engine (OKE) for deployment of the WebLogic Server domain. By default, OKE nodes are provisioned using AMD (Intel-compatible) CPUs. This will require using a new feature in WKT UI 2.0 that supports cross-architecture images. Rancher Desktop (and most other Docker providers) rely on QEMU (Quick Emulator) to support cross-architecture capabilities. As of the writing of this guide, Rancher Desktop with QEMU cross-architecture builds are not as reliable as we would like. Our advice is to open the Rancher Desktop Preferences window, navigate to Virtual Machine -&gt; Emulation, and change the Virtual Machine Type from QEMU to VZ. You can also check the VZ Option to Enable Rosetta support, though this is probably not required. This will provide a more reliable cross-architecture container image building environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Select the Project Settings</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/project-settings/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/project-settings/index.html</guid>
      <description>Start WKT UI.&#xA;WKT UI uses the concept of a project that is like a project in an Integrated Development Environment (IDE). You will create a new project.&#xA;Using the File menu, select New Project, choose a directory, and enter the file name todo-list.wktproj.&#xA;At this point, you will be on the Project Settings page that will look something like the one shown in the following image.&#xA;Note: If you are not running on macOS, you will not see this top-most panel: For macOS, do you need to add directories to the PATH or define other environment variables for Docker/Podman or Kubernetes?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create the WebLogic Deploy Tooling model</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/create-wdt-model/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/create-wdt-model/index.html</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Deploy Tooling project provides a set of single-purpose tools for performing lifecycle operations of WebLogic Server domains. These tools work off a model of the domain. The model contains three types of files:&#xA;Model file – A YAML description of the domain that is aligned with WebLogic Scripting Tool (WLST) offline folders and attributes. Variables file – An optional Java properties file that contains key/value pairs where the key matches with a token placed in the model file. Archive file – An optional ZIP file that contains any file artifacts that need to exist in the domain, for example, a WAR file that contains the binaries for a Web application. For more detailed WDT information, see the WebLogic Deploy Tooling documentation .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create images with the WebLogic Image Tool</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/create-images-with-wit/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/create-images-with-wit/index.html</guid>
      <description>WKT UI uses the WebLogic Image Tool (WIT) to build container images. Each Oracle Fusion Middleware (FMW) Domain Target Location option has its own image requirements.&#xA;Model-in-Image (MII) – This approach puts Java and WebLogic Server into one image, which WKT UI calls the primary image, and WDT and the WDT model files into a separate image, known as the auxiliary image. In this document, we refer to this as MII with Auxiliary Image. Since WKT UI 2.0.0 removed support for MII without the use of an Auxiliary Image, all references to Model-in-Image or MII are meant to reference Model-in-Image with Auxiliary Image. Domain-on-PV (DoPV) – This approach uses a single image with Java and FMW in it. The domain is created on the persistent volume by external means or by using a Domain Creation Image, which is conceptually similar to an auxiliary image. A domain creation image, like an auxiliary image, has a WDT installer and WDT model files to define the domain. WebLogic Kubernetes Operator uses the domain creation image to create the initial domain on the persistent volume only if the domain directory does not already exist. Once the domain is created, all configuration changes are managed by the domain administrator, similar to how on premises domains are managed. The only difference is that server lifecycle is managed by WebLogic Kubernetes Operator and Kubernetes. Both MII with Auxiliary Image and Domain-on-PV have an image containing only software (Java and WebLogic Server/FMW) with no configuration. This provides several important, operational advantages:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-kubernetes/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-kubernetes/index.html</guid>
      <description>These Quick Start guide sections are for users interested in using a Kubernetes cluster. Anyone using OpenShift should follow this track.&#xA;Configure your Kubernetes client (kubectl) to connect to the Kubernetes cluster. Install WebLogic Kubernetes Operator . Deploy the Domain . Install and Configure the Ingress Controller and add ingress routes to allow access to the WebLogic domain from outside the Kubernetes cluster. Access the ToDo List application .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-summary/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-summary/index.html</guid>
      <description>By following the steps in this Quick Start guide, you:&#xA;Configured WKT UI and set up a new project. Manually created and edited a WDT model of a WebLogic domain using the Design View for visual editing of the model and the Code View for viewing and editing model-related files. Pulled a prebuilt (primary) image from the Oracle Container Registry and then manually created an auxiliary image. Deployed a MySQL database. Installed the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator to deploy your domain, then installed and configured an ingress controller to expose the sample application and provide its access in a browser window. Optionally, used the instructions in the Advanced section to discover the domain model offline or online remotely. In summary, you used comprehensive WKT UI functionality to take an on-premises, sample WebLogic domain and deploy it in Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-advanced/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/setup/quickstart/qs-advanced/index.html</guid>
      <description>Use the these sections to walk-through examples of offline discovery and online remote discovery.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>