<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Release Notes on WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Release Notes on WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.6.3</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.3/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.6.3  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #294 - Updated Model Design View to use WebLogic Remote Console 2.4.8  Bug Fixes None
Known Issues  On Linux, the open and save dialogs open behind the main application window. This is due to Electron bug 32857. When deploying a Verrazzano application, the Get Application Status button only checks the status of the project&amp;rsquo;s Verrazzano component containing the WebLogic domain specification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.7.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.7.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.7.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.7.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #294 - Updated application to be compatible with WebLogic Deploy Tooling 4.x.  Bug Fixes None
Known Issues  On Mac, the embedded version of WDT 4.1.0 does not include the jansi-2.4.1 JAR file that WDT&amp;rsquo;s interactive Model Help tool requires due to an Apple requirement to sign the native code inside this third-party JAR file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.7.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.7.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.7.1/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.7.1  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #297 - Removed the default value for the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator image tag so that the default image specified by the Helm chart is used.  Bug Fixes  #296 - Changed the API Group for traefik to be compatible with Traefik 3.0  Known Issues  On Mac, the embedded version of WDT 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.6.2</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.2/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.6.2  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #287 - Added support for WebLogic Kubernetes Operator domain specification&amp;rsquo;s precreateService setting.  Bug Fixes  #286 - Fixed an issue related to SSL termination and pass through Ingress resource generation.  Known Issues  On Linux, the open and save dialogs open behind the main application window. This is due to Electron bug 32857.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.6.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.1/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.6.1  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #281 - Fixed issue with Ingress Controller shell script not using elif. #282 - Fixed issue with busy dialog referencing &amp;ldquo;auxiliary image&amp;rdquo; while building a domain creation image. #283 - Fixed a typo in the Verrazzano application page in its reference to the Manual Scaler trait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.5.3</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.3/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.5.3  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #242 - Added initial (very minimal) internationalization support bundles. #245 - Added an Ingress Controller Service Type field that can be used when installing an ingress controller to a Kubernetes cluster without a load balancer.  Bug Fixes  #241 - Fixed a bug with the WebLogic Image Tool&amp;rsquo;s --wdtHome argument when it ended with weblogic-deploy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.6.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.6.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.6.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  This release has major usability changes to clearly delineate the following use cases:
 A project that contains a WDT model A project that does not have a model but uses an &amp;ldquo;external image&amp;rdquo; that contains a model A project with no model  When actions are not relevant to the use case, action buttons and Go menu items are hidden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.5.2</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.2/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.5.2  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #232 - Fixed an issue in the Verrazzano Application page where the component&amp;rsquo;s Ingress Trait Rule destination names were not properly converted to legal Kubernetes names so that they would match the generated service names when the domain, cluster, or server names combinations had more than one disallowed characters in them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.5.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.1/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.5.1  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #229 - Fixed issue in Domain resource generation on Windows inserting a path with Windows separators  Known Issues  In the Model Design View, changing the Source Path and Plan Path fields for existing App Deployments and Shared Libraries is broken in this release. To work around it, either remove and recreate the deployment or use the Model Code View&amp;rsquo;s Model Editor and Archive Editor to make the appropriate changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.5.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.5.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.5.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #202 - Added support for Verrazzano 1.5.0+ (which uses WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 4.0.0+). #204 - Updated the Archive Editor to align with WebLogic Deploy Tooling 3.0.0+ changes to the archive format. #205 - Added support for installing the optional Verrazzano component Argo CD with Verrazzano 1.5.0+. #205 - Added support to configure Kubernetes connectivity data for Verrazzano managed clusters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.4.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.4.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.4.1/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.4.1  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #192: Add the ability to install and work with older versions of operator using the latest published Helm chart.  Bug Fixes  Resolved issue Discover Model issue introduced in 1.4.0 by picking up the fix in WebLogic Deploy Tooling 2.4.1. Resolved issue with Deploy Domain failing due to a WebLogic Kubernetes Operator error from the new conversion/validating webhook (fix in a new published version of the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.4.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.4.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.4.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features  #173: Added support for WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 4.0. While it is now the default, versions 3.3+ are still supported.  Other Changes  #175: Added Zoom In, Zoom Out, and Actual Size menu options to the Window menu. #178: Integrated the Prepare Model action with the changes in WebLogic Deploy Tooling 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.3.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.3.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.3.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features  Support for creating and deploying the Verrazzano component for the WebLogic domain, and an application that references it.  Other Changes  Updated the WebLogic Remote Console integration to support version 2.4.0. Added support for specifying node selectors when installing the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator and deploying the WebLogic domain, either directly or as a Verrazzano component.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.2.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.2.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes  Major New Features  Model Design View added via integration with the WebLogic Remote Console 2.3.0. Users must download and install the WebLogic Remote Console version 2.3.x.  Other Changes  Added a new installer for macOS ARM. #141: Added support for WDT online remote discovery.  Bug Fixes  #107: Resolved an issue where the Save As functionality was not handling the archive file properly if there were no pending updates to the archive file (Jira WKTUI-322).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.1.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.1.1/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.1.1  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features No new features.
Other Changes  Revamped the Ingress Route editing mechanism:  Added busy dialog while fetching existing service data from the domain&amp;rsquo;s Kubernetes namespace prior to opening the route edit dialog. Added placeholders to the Target Service and Target Port fields to clarify the current state of these fields when no value is selected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.1.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-toolkit-ui/release/release-1.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 1.1.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features  Updated macOS environment control to specify extra environment settings to pass down to Docker/Podman, kubectl, and Helm invocations. Bundling WebLogic Deploy Tooling 2.0.0. See WDT release notes for details. New Validate Model action that leverages WDT 2.0 changes to validate the model files and reports any validation errors it finds. Updated Prepare Model action that leverages WDT 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
